Today I am going to eat the food
that bloggers have
praised so much all day and find out if it is
really worthy of praise.  So brother, first of all let
us come to Dolman Aunty Momos.
Brother, as much as people have criticized their momos, they have
praised their Chinese spreader equally.  So today we are also going to test it and
tell you how it is.  Brother, according to some people he
is good and according to some people he is
bad.  But according to me, the
good one is bad.  After that we come to
half fried.  Brother, its owner is
himself a YouTuber, so it is worth praising him.
And brother, we had got Tushar Bhai's favourite
Chilli Chapato, which he
keeps praising in his videos every day.
Eat momos, honey chilli potato, this is my
brother, when we tried Tushar Bhai's favourite half
fried chilli chapatti, brother, I am
telling you the truth, I enjoyed eating it.
Finally we come to eat KGF Bhaiya's
dumplings.  Brother, their dumplings are
quite famous in Siar Park.  We had a
plate of paneer momos prepared for them.  But when
I tried their momos, I really enjoyed
eating them because it was
stuffed with paneer.  Now quickly
comment what should I do next?